♪ Ground Control to Major Tom ♪
♪ Seven... Six ♪
♪ Commencing countdown engines on ♪
♪ Three... Two ♪
♪ Check ignition and may God's love
Be with you ♪
♪ This is Ground Control to Major Tom ♪
♪ You've really made the grade ♪
♪ And the papers want to know
Whose shirts you wear ♪
♪ Now it's time to leave
The capsule if you dare ♪
♪ This is Major Tom to Ground Control ♪
♪ I'm stepping through the door ♪
♪ And I'm floating
In a most peculiar way ♪
♪ And the stars
Look very different today ♪
♪ For here
Am I sitting in a tin can ♪
♪ Far above the world ♪
♪ Planet Earth is blue
And there's nothing I can do ♪
♪ Though I'm past
One hundred thousand miles ♪
♪ I'm feeling very still ♪
♪ And I think my spaceship knows
Which way to go ♪
♪ Tell my wife I love her very much
She knows ♪
♪ Ground Control to Major Tom
Your circuit's dead ♪
♪ There's something wrong
Can you hear me Major Tom ♪
♪ Can you hear me Major Tom ♪
♪ Can you
Here am I floating round my tin can ♪
♪ Far above the moon ♪
♪ Planet Earth is blue
And there's nothing I can do ♪
The Alpha intergalactic space station
has reached critical mass in orbit.
Its weight and size now pose
a serious threat to Mother Earth.
In its great wisdom, the Central Committee
has decided to use all resources necessary
to release this space station
from the Earth's gravity.
Its new course is set
for the Magellan Current.
Like the great explorer Magellan,
the Alpha Station
will journey into the unknown.
A symbol of our values and knowledge.
It will carry a message of peace and unity
to the farthest reaches of the universe.
Our thoughts and prayers go with you.
Godspeed and good luck.
Ah...
Let us give back to nature,
that which she gave to us.
Give this pearl
to my daughter, Princess Lïho.
Dad?!
It's broken!
Lïho!
- You okay?
- Yeah. Just a...
bad dream.
No.
- Hey!
- But I feel better now.
Don't you think we should run
through our assignment?
That's the last thing I feel like doing.
Not very professional, Major.
Look, I scored a perfect 200
on my last memory test.
Impressive. Unfortunately you've forgotten
something rather important today.
- What's that?
- My birthday.
Hey!
What can I do to make it up to you?
Beginning descent in three minutes.
Nothing that you can get done
in three minutes.
Come on.
Don't start what you can't finish.
Landing
on planet Kyrian in five minutes.
Sorry. Hey, look.
I know you're attracted to me.
Why deny the obvious?
- It's obvious?
- Yeah, sure.
Little Goody Two-shoes
with an Ivy League education
are always attracted to galaxy-hopping
bad boys like me.
My Ivy League education taught me
to steer clear from bad boys like you.
Yeah, well, you're not going to find
better than me on the market.
Straight up. Take a good look.
Handsome, intelligent...
- Modest.
- Brave.
- Suicidal.
- Determined.
- Pig-headed.
- Faithful.
- To yourself.
- Yeah, and to you.
- You're my partner.
- Yeah, don't forget it.
Look, why don't you think with your heart
and not your head for once?
I don't wanna be another name
on your list of conquests,
thank you very much.
What are you talking about? What list?
Alex, can we see the playlist, please?
No, no. No, no, no. Hey.
Most of those are coworkers,
and that's it.
Coworkers?
Right, where's my picture then?
They mean nothing to me. Okay?
I took a few detours when I was younger.
Your last detour was not so long ago.
Yeah, but with you it's different.
And you know it.
I want my heart to belong
to you and no one else.
My heart will belong to a man
who will erase his playlist for me.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm that man.
Look, we both know
you're quite a ladykiller.
So why do you lose interest in a girl
as soon as you win her heart?
'Cause I'm looking for the perfect woman.
But you've never stopped to look.
That's not a crime.
No, it's not a crime.
But just admit it,
you're scared of commitment.
Me? Scared of commitment?
Are you kidding me?
Nine years in the service.
Impeccable record.
Seven medals of honor.
Never lost a partner.
Yeah, until now.
Refuel complete.
Alex, did you enter the coordinates?
I took that liberty,
so you could both
enjoy the beach a while longer.
- Oh, thank you.
- You are welcome.
You will be leaving exospace
in 30 seconds.
- You wanna take us down?
- Yes, sir.
Alex, will you pull up my brain charts
for the past 10 minutes?
I had a weird dream.
See anything abnormal?
Your cerebral activity
is a little more intense than usual.
- You received external waves.
- Explain.
These waves
don't come from your memory.
Somebody is sending you the images.
- Do you know who? Where they come from?
- Negative.
They could come from the present or past.
And from anywhere in the universe.
Leaving exospace.
Three, two, one... exit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Easy, easy.
- We're late.
Yeah, well, better late than dead.
Do you wanna drive?
Whoa! Put your hand back on the joystick.
Laureline, put your hands
back on the joystick.
Laureline, will you please put your hand
back on the joystick?
Will you stop complaining
about my driving?
Yes, I'm sorry. You're a great driver.
You're the best driver
in the entire universe.
Aw. Thank you.
- Intercom activated.
- Thanks.
Touchdown on Kyrian in two minutes.
Minister on line.
- Sir?
- Agents Valerian and Laureline,
I trust you've studied the assignment.
So as soon as you land,
recover the Converter
and bring it to Alpha
for a top-secret operation.
The Converter is the last
creature of his species,
- so we're counting on you.
- Yes, sir.
Captain Gibson has further details.
And please, put on some
more appropriate clothing.
Good idea. Leaving manual.
Manual disarmed.
Intercom activated.
Here they come. Intruder 980.
Check parameters.
Two people on board. No parasites.
Where's the band?
You plan on going on a mission
dressed like that?
We're supposed to mingle
with tourists, aren't we?
What do you expect us to wear?
A panda suit?
Nice hat.
Major, this mission is in-and-out.
You enter Big Market,
you find the suspect's store,
and you team up with Sergeant Cooper.
- I only work with my partner.
- Hi.
We're a team.
Sergeant Laureline will arrive at the drop
in exactly 20 minutes, and you will have
10 seconds to make the transfer.
Didn't you read the memo?
Yeah. Of course.
You better have.
How about we look at the memo
one last time?
Can't hurt.
Think you can survive
20 minutes without me?
How could I possibly?
Go on. Be careful.
Oh, you must be right.
I completely forgot,
I have a question for you.
Shoot.
What?
Will you marry me?
- Not funny.
- Laureline, I'm serious.
I've been thinking about what you said
earlier and you're right.
I need to move onward and upward.
I need to commit.
Here? Just like that?
Yeah. Why not?
They sell a zillion things here.
I'm sure we can find a priest
who'd be happy to oblige.
Go.
Okay, let's go.
We remind you
that if you want to enjoy
the experience of Big Market,
you must put on equipment
available to you.
Thank you.
Welcome, everybody. Welcome.
Please gather around, gather around.
Now, my name is Thaziit,
and I am your guide for today, okay?
Now, whose first time
is this at Big Market?
Lovely, lovely. Wonderful, wonderful.
Now, let me remind you
that Big Market is in another dimension.
You won't be able to see it
without your helmet,
or touch it without your gloves.
For there are nearly a million stores
in Big Market.
Yes, okay, we have one hour.
Now, please watch the letters at the top,
and verify that the "U"
for Human is full green, okay?
So, everybody please, get together,
right behind your guide, whose name is?
- Thaziit!
- Thaziit! Come on, let's go!
Okay, follow me.
Please, put your helmets on.
Come through the gates. Okay?
Activate your system. Wonderful.
Do not leave your helmet.
System activated.
Whoa...
Welcome to Big Market.
Hi.
Yes, sure, of course. Bill?
Can I have my camera, please? Thank you.
Say cheese.
Thank you, Bill.
- You're good.
- Thanks.
Hey, Hey.
♪ Come with me ♪
♪ Stand by me ♪
- ♪ Stars are sweet ♪
- Good luck.
- What the hell are you doing, soldier?
- Sorry, sir.
Keep an eye on the guy, all right?
Yes, sir.
Please be careful
down the stairs.
Come on, everyone.
- Just think baby a million stores.
- Yeah.
Only stuff that we can carry, okay?
- I promise.
- All right.
All right, drop in 12 minutes.
Copy that.
I found the suspect's store.
Good. Sergeant Cooper will help you
get in and recover the stolen property.
- Major Valerian.
- Sergeant Cooper.
As you read in the memo, you need glasses
to see the other dimension,
and a trans-matter box
to bring anything there.
- Especially a gun.
- Authorized.
Put this on.
Enter your genetic code
on the front keypad.
To come back, enter your genetic code
on the back keypad.
- Clear?
- Crystal.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Hey, Tsûuri. Good to see you again.
Please, sit down.
Do you have what we asked for?
Yeah, yeah.
But it was a toughie.
I lost a lot of personnel
getting this for you.
But this thing is priceless.
What can you give me in exchange?
Amazing.
I never thought
I'd see one in my lifetime.
You'll have hundreds of them.
Just as soon as
you give us what we came for.
Oh...
That's where I have
a slight problem, my friends.
If you're going to knock out
copies of this baby for me,
why shouldn't I do it for myself?
Hey, hey. Easy, my little lambs.
We absolutely need this Converter.
You know we are fighting
for a noble cause.
I know. And I'm fighting
for a noble cause, too.
Mine.
You have 10 seconds to drop your guns.
Hmm?
Showtime.
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Federal Agent Valerian.
Sorry to interrupt this great deal,
but I'm also here for a noble cause.
It's called the law.
Hey, haven't I seen you guys
somewhere before?
Hey, I'm not running a tearoom here.
What do you want from me?
Igon Siruss, you stand accused of stealing
a Mül Converter
belonging to the Federation.
But before I drag your ass in,
I have to recover the stolen property.
- All right, how we doing?
- Almost there.
Valerian, I'll be to your left
at 3 o'clock.
- Three meters away.
- Got you.
Guys, don't move.
Now, take it nice and easy
and push it into the box.
- Converter in the box.
- Copy.
Undetected. Back to base.
- Good job.
- Copy that.
- Valerian, get out of here.
- I'm on my way.
I'll find you, Federal Agent Valerian.
Wherever you are in the universe,
I'll find you.
And I will kill you.
Good luck.
Valerian's in trouble.
Mission takes priority. Keep going.
- Cooper, cover him.
- Copy that.
Seek and destroy. Top priority.
Target's photograph to follow.
- Valerian, how we doing?
- Good.
I think I lost them.
- Are you thirsty?
- No, thank you.
I'm to your left, 200 feet away.
My keypad's broken.
- You need some energy?
- No, thank you.
The box is broken.
I can't get my arm back.
Hey, you need a lawyer?
Federal agent on duty. Leave me alone.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yeah.
Valerian, what are you doing?
Da!
Very funny.
What's your name?
- Da.
- Da?
Come here. Come here. Try this.
It's way more fun.
Da.
So long.
Da! Da! Da! Da!
Yeah, yeah, there's a time
for everything, kid.
Don't you have homework to do?
All right, go get yourself
cleaned up, run to Mommy.
- Mommy?
- Da.
Watch out!
Sorry!
To retrieve
your purchases, please place your items
in the transmatter box
and enter your DNA code. Thank you.
Amazing. And so practical.
Useless, you mean.
You don't even know what
you'll do with the darn thing.
Don't be such a grouch. It's decorative.
Try to be civilized for once.
Civilized. Yeah, sure.
- Watch out!
- Sorry!
Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey, thanks a lot!
Sorry!
- I didn't see the wall.
- Need some help?
I just need you to fix my arm, thanks.
I suppose, since you asked for my hand,
you should probably get yours back first.
- Is that a yes?
- Don't move.
How can I help you if you keep moving?
Will you just hurry up, please?
Please keep still.
You've been detected.
Uh... Sorry to bother you.
I'm out of ammo and there's
three headed my way.
Give me one second.
I don't have a second.
- Okay, you're good.
- Thanks!
I don't know what I'd do without you.
To retrieve
your purchases, please place your items
in the transmatter box,
and enter your DNA code.
Thank you.
Fetch.
You've been detected.
Keep moving, don't change course.
- What are we supposed to do?
- Run.
- Zito, cover them.
- Yes, sir!
Get! Get in!
Come on, let's go! Go, go, go!
I'm coming, I'm coming! I'm coming!
Zito, get that thing off our backs.
I got it.
Guys, take it out! Take it out!
Alex, we need you right now!
Let's go!
Shoot. He ruined my dress.
Alex, I'm gonna take over on manual.
Prepare to enter exospace.
You know the coordinates
for the rendezvous?
Yeah, I'm just deciphering them.
- Alex, what was that?
- We have a stowaway.
Oh, great. Hold on.
Major Valerian, you're running
nearly 20 minutes late.
Yeah, well, time flies
when you're having fun.
- We have the Mül Converter.
- Excellent.
Now perhaps you can tell me
what you're doing 17 light-years
- from your rendezvous?
- Yeah. It sounds pretty grim
when you put it like that.
But when I say we'll be there in
- nine minutes, does that sound better?
- I'll inform the Commander
that you're behind schedule,
and pass on your apology.
Yeah, you do that.
Leaving exospace in five seconds.
Somebody's gonna land with a bang.
Okay, let's have a look at you.
Not at me, tiger. Come on.
Don't be scared. I'll look after you.
Come on.
Hello.
Wow.
You have the most incredible eyes.
Okay, you're a little scabby.
So why don't we get you a nice treatment
so you can get your mojo back?
Sound good?
Come on.
Some high-grade uranium
and you'll be good as new.
Hang on, tiger.
Alex?
Analyze this, please.
Power, 20 megatons?
Indeed. There's 10 times more power
in that pearl than in our entire ship.
Where's it come from?
From Mül, a planet that was
in the constellation QN34.
- Was?
- Yes.
The planet no longer exists,
and hasn't for 30 years.
Let's see what it looked like.
Abundant vegetation,
a few primal species,
but of no particular interest.
The one in my dream
was pretty... interesting.
Zoom in.
- Use our access codes.
- I'm afraid that won't be enough, Major.
Access is restricted.
To what rank?
General. Five stars.
The creature in my dream, she had a pearl
just like that on her neck.
Noted, Major.
Leaving exospace in one minute.
He's very cute, you know.
And a real charmer.
You may have some competition.
I'm fine with competition.
Hey, I'm still waiting for your answer.
I know I can be full of myself sometimes,
but I'm dead serious about my proposal.
We have to complete the mission, Major.
There's still the top secret
part to attend to.
Or is your perfect memory
failing you again?
Seat belt.
You know what?
I'm gonna ask for 10 days'
leave right now,
and I'm gonna take you to the most
beautiful beach in the whole universe.
A real beach this time.
The perfect place for a honeymoon.
- Ten seconds.
- The honeymoon comes after the wedding.
You know that, right?
- Really?
- Yup.
Three, two, one. Decelerating.
Whoa!
Alex, what are you doing?
Sorry, too much traffic.
- Do you want me to drive?
- Nope. No, no. No, thank you.
Welcome to Alpha,
the City of a Thousand Planets.
Alex, can you update us?
I'd be delighted to.
The Alpha Station has grown 7% this year,
and since it left the terrestrial orbit,
it has traveled almost 700 million miles.
Population?
Almost 30 million. 3,236 species
from the four corners
of the universe live on board,
pooling their knowledge and cultures.
Over 5,000 languages spoken, not counting
the various computer languages.
Demographics?
To the south are the submerged parts,
with 800 species living
in all kinds of liquids.
Such as the peaceful Poulong farmers
who grow cobalt.
To the north, we have gaseous lands
dominated by the Azin Mö,
whose extreme sensitivity
makes them specialists
in neurosciences and molecular components.
They can build cells of any kind.
To the east of them,
the large colony of Omelites.
They control information technology,
finance, and banking.
Finally, to the west,
in a pressurized atmosphere,
we have 9 million humans
and compatible species.
Home sweet home.
The economy has been
in shambles for a year.
- Do you want a quick summary?
- No. That's enough excitement for one day.
Intruder XB982.
Authorization to dock in Section 1.
- VIP access.
- Oh.
We're famous.
You're late, Major.
Sorry, sir. Things got a bit
more complicated than we expected.
Prepare for the worst
and you won't be disappointed.
And neither will I.
I'll keep that in mind, sir.
And you, have you checked the Converter?
He's in great shape.
May I ask what's going on?
Follow me.
Declassify.
A year ago, we discovered
a radioactive zone
right in the middle of the station.
No signal of any kind
could get through it.
We sent several probes, none came back.
So we sent in a special unit.
Its mission was to get as close
to the zone as possible,
and define the nature of the threat.
And?
No one came back alive.
- Any idea who attacked them?
- No.
This is the situation today.
The air in the zone is unbreathable,
highly contaminated.
And it continues to grow. Like a tumor.
A tumor we have to cut out
as soon as we can.
If we don't, and this cancer
keeps spreading,
it will destroy Alpha in less than a week.
Commander, who would have
any reason to destroy Alpha?
Practically every living
species is represented here.
This is a weapon of mass destruction, and
behind every weapon, there is a killer.
It doesn't matter who it is. It's a threat
to us all. It must be eliminated.
Through here.
- Commander.
- Minister.
The Council has given you the green light.
But we strongly recommend
that international law
and the civil rights
of all concerned should be respected.
Of course. I shall see to it personally.
Agents Valerian and Laureline
will be responsible
for your personal protection.
Sir, that won't be necessary.
I have a unit of K-tron
that I personally trained...
It's a direct order from
the government, Commander.
The two agents need to report
on the outcome of the operations.
As you wish.
Gentlemen, lady, good luck.
Since we have to be on the same team,
you mind giving us an update
on the operation?
I'll be speaking to the Security Council
in a few minutes.
You'll have all the details
you need to know.
This is gonna be a lot of fun.
Hey, handsome.
You're looking a lot better.
You know, I remember learning
about you guys at school.
I'm dying to find out
if what they say is true.
Okay.
Wow.
I need to take you shopping with me.
Wait for me here.
- Anything?
- Not yet.
We haven't got a peep out of him,
but I'm trying something new.
One more hour.
If he hasn't talked, finish him off.
Yes, sir.
If anything goes wrong
with this operation,
you know what you have to do.
Wow.
Looks like you're taking
my protection very seriously.
His protection, actually.
He's one of a kind.
You're sure he needs to come along
on such a dangerous mission?
The Mül Converter is capable
of reproducing
any conceivable product in record time.
It will come in very handy
if we have to negotiate.
With the army of K-trons
under your command,
I'm surprised negotiating's on the table.
You take care of my security, Major.
I'll take care of any negotiations.
- Give it to me.
- I don't think that's a very good idea.
For your personal security,
why don't you let Agent Laureline
look after the little guy for safekeeping?
I don't think so, Major.
It's against protocol.
I am the highest ranking...
That animal is the last living specimen
of its species.
The whole universe is after it.
That's why Major Valerian
would rather I held onto it.
All right.
Just don't leave my side.
Commander, the Council is waiting.
Okay, let's do this.
Stay here.
En route to the meeting.
Received, General.
You stay on backup.
I'll take the front line.
Yes, sir.
Delegates, thank you
for answering the call so quickly.
As the elected representative
of the Human Federation,
I have called this meeting
of the Alpha Security Council
to update you regarding the state
of emergency we find ourselves in.
As you all know,
the heart of historic Alpha Station
has been contaminated by a force
whose power we do not know the origins of.
The Human Federation has launched
several small military attacks
in order to ascertain
the severity of the threat,
but these have all ended in failure.
And with some significant
losses among our troops.
In light of this alarming
and growing threat to us all,
the Human Federation is seeking...
Everything okay?
You're missing out.
I'm having a lot of fun.
Yeah. Don't worry,
we'll be on the beach soon.
I can now answer
any questions you may have
about the details of the operation.
13th Battalion, Special Assaults Division.
- There she is.
- I told you she was there.
That's all I need.
Agent Laureline.
- What?
- Doghan Daguis.
Oh.
- Nice to see you again.
- Agent Laureline.
As resplendent as ever.
Just tell me what you want.
We go where work calls.
We speak over 5,000 languages.
Which can be handy in a party like this.
Need our services?
I have my own personal translator.
Now move.
Ask them if they have intel on Mül.
Planet Mül, ring any bells?
A highly sensitive matter.
The best person to speak to...
Would be Major Samk.
Alex?
Major Samk died a year ago.
Well, yes, a most curious demise.
- That was not fully explained.
- Murder some might call it.
Major Samk was an expert on Planet Mül.
He took all
that precious information...
To the grave with him.
What a waste.
If you receive any intel on this planet,
- we're interested.
- It would be a pleasure
- to work for you, Laureline.
- Before we go...
- We would like to give you...
- Some info.
For free.
- For free?
- Mmm-hmm.
You guys must be sick.
- The Converter is precious.
- And highly sought-after.
- Mercenaries will come...
- To retrieve it...
- Sooner than you think.
- What kind of mercenaries?
- The first tip was free.
- You must pay for more.
But you get a discount, of course.
General, we have an alert on Section B.
- Alex, what's that?
- A dozen individuals approaching.
- What kind of individuals?
- Undetectable for now.
It appears your info just lost its value.
Now get out of my face.
- Move, pigeons.
- She just called us pigeons.
- What's a pigeon?
- I don't know.
- Where are they coming from?
- Everywhere.
They're going through the walls.
Alex, I need to know
the attackers' identity.
Everyone, please evacuate.
I cannot read their DNA.
What?
Sir, the door's locked. We can't get out.
- Laureline.
- I'm coming.
- Evacuate the Commander.
- Copy that.
General, secure that door.
- Commander.
- What's going on?
- We need to evacuate.
- Let's go.
- It's not working.
- What? Alex, open the door.
- What was that?
- The Pearls.
They took the Commander.
Here, take this. Free the General.
Go to the command room
and track them from there.
Okay.
- Are we back to full power?
- Yes, sir, just now.
Everybody, back to your posts!
Status on Major Valerian?
Level 5 emergency.
Confirmed.
Valerian, I've got you on visual.
Okay,
but I've lost track of them.
Try to locate the Commander.
Okay, I've got him.
He's near the docking bay,
so he must be headed towards the vessel.
Okay, what's the shortest way there?
North-northeast, 113 degrees.
Sixty, 70, 80, 90.
That leads me straight into a wall.
You said you wanted the shortest way.
It may be the shortest way,
but it's not the easiest.
Keep going. You're almost there.
They've reached another ship.
No tags, unknown model.
Valerian, they've boarded. Change of plan.
A hundred and forty degrees east.
Alex will pick you up.
- 81?
- That's it. 81, straight.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- 81? You're sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Because I just went through
and I'm falling in space.
Sorry, my mistake. It was number 18.
That's okay. We all make mistakes.
Any idea to get me out of here?
Alex, pick him up on 81.
I'm in. Close it.
Bring on the beach.
I'm not sure where you come from,
but I know where I'm gonna send you.
Valerian, hold still.
We're analyzing its system of defense.
Major, their protective shield
is too sophisticated.
You won't get through.
I'm gonna try something bigger.
Shit!
Laureline, which one
has the Commander on board?
Nine o'clock,
lower level. Hurry up.
That's the one. Don't lose it.
Valerian, be careful.
The Intruder's too big to follow them.
I'm gonna take the SkyJet.
Okay.
Okay, Valerian, you're near the Dead Zone.
Reel them in before I lose you.
I'm working on it.
Valerian, you need to go faster.
Valerian, you've got 10 seconds
before I lose you.
Take that.
Who's the clever one now?
Valerian, you've got five seconds.
Oh, no. Not me.
- Valerian?
- I can't slow 'em down.
Come on. Come on.
Entering Red Zone.
Valerian, do you hear me?
Laureline! I'm losing control!
Laureline!
Valerian, answer me. Valerian, answer me.
- Major, respond.
- Alex, can you help?
There's too much interference.
I've lost the Major's signal.
Valerian? Valerian?
Valerian, do you copy?
We've lost him.
Sergeant, where are you going?
To grab my SkyJet.
- You won't be going after him.
- Why not?
That zone is under enemy
control. It's too dangerous.
An enemy that we don't know!
An enemy that's just attacked us!
By putting us to sleep
and not hurting a single one of us!
Why would they spare our lives?
Give me one good reason.
I don't know.
Valerian has seen these creatures before.
They are from Planet Mül.
Planet Mül was destroyed 30 years ago.
You're not making any sense.
It's our mission
that doesn't make sense, sir!
Someone is lying to us,
and while you find out who,
I'm going to go save my partner.
General, Major Valerian
is an invaluable agent.
You cannot afford to lose him.
No, I can't afford to lose
both of you in one day.
Restrain her.
Put us on high alert,
and find me the Commander.
Yes, sir.
Listen, I don't wanna tell you guys
how to do your jobs,
but don't you think you should cuff me?
Firstly, because it's protocol,
but secondly,
because I'm very tempted to escape.
Good job, boys.
We need to talk.
Oh, it's dark in here.
- Ow!
- Sorry.
If you don't help me find Valerian,
then this bullet's gonna find you.
- You're up first.
- No, no, no, no.
- It's to avoid such situations...
- That all of our information...
- Is divided three ways.
- Kill one of us...
- And you kill the information.
- What a pity that would be.
Okay. You're gonna have to
give me credit, though,
- 'cause I don't have much on me.
- Oh, how tiresome.
- If the Commander were here...
- He could use the Converter to pay us.
But he's been abducted...
Precisely because he had the Converter
on him.
Unless, for security reasons...
Someone else was carrying it on them.
How in space did you get that info?
- It's not info.
- Just deduction.
- We know how humans work.
- They're all so predictable.
Clearly you've never met a woman.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- Calm down.
What do you want to know?
Valerian's exact location.
Hard to tell.
But we know how to track him down...
With complete precision.
- How much?
- One hundred baduls.
- Each.
- Forget about it.
This is all I have.
Diamonds are less valuable than baduls.
The negotiation is over.
- We trust you.
- And under the circumstances...
- We accept the deal.
- Good.
Now take me to Valerian. Now.
Follow us.
Philips, head to the location
where the Major disappeared.
Milo, track down Agent Laureline
and bring her in.
- Neza, inform the Minister.
- Yes, sir.
Just give me a few minutes, please.
Declassify.
I need all information on the Planet Mül.
Well, who has authority over this file?
Here we are.
I do not like this place.
Here.
I've got a bad feeling
about this idea of yours.
Bingo.
What do you want?
- We'd like to go fishing...
- For a cortex jellyfish.
Male, if possible.
Nah, it's not the season.
Here.
- Males are harder to catch.
- And here.
Welcome aboard.
Uh...
The thing, down.
- The... Down. The thing, down.
- This one?
There. Bromosaurs.
- Are they dangerous?
- Not really.
You just have to be careful
they don't inhale you.
There, that one is a male.
How can you tell?
Oh, they're much smaller than the females.
How do you know that that one
has a jellyfish on it?
All males do.
The Bromosaurs blow out pure water,
which the jellyfish can't do without.
That's why they live
on them all year round,
and that's where they get
their hypersensitivity from.
Soft as silk.
Can I help? I'm a good driver.
- Seat belt.
- What?
Seat belt.
I thought you said
they weren't aggressive.
Except when you take their little buddy.
Great.
I'm Bob, by the way.
Hi.
There's no time to lose.
The cortex jellyfish
is extremely fragile.
Show it images of Valerian...
And it will show you what it has seen.
Sure, but how?
- You have to put it...
- On your head...
Down to your shoulders.
- You're kidding?
- Never when we're working.
- Through a kind of osmosis...
- You'll be able to communicate.
- But be very careful...
- Not to stay under there...
Longer than a minute.
Because then it starts to feed...
On your memory.
Great. Anything else I should know before
I voluntarily stick my head on his mouth?
Actually, it's not his mouth.
- You can begin.
- Good luck.
- Don't forget.
- One minute.
Not a second more.
I knew I had it in here somewhere.
There we are. Aha!
Pe-ew!
There we go.
This is so exciting.
Valerian?
I only work with my partner.
Valerian, answer me!
What can I do
to make it up to you?
Thirty seconds.
Valerian, answer me!
Take that.
Laureline! I'm losing control!
Valerian!
- Valerian!
- Laureline!
Forty seconds.
Valerian!
- Fifty seconds! Get out!
- Now!
Fifty-five seconds!
Valerian!
Valerian.
- Beautiful.
- Incredible.
- One minute...
- And 10 seconds.
A record.
Okay...
"L.630.E-S-U-L deactivated."
Any idea what that means, guys?
- Level 630 East.
- Most likely a sulfate pipe.
Deactivated, apparently.
Okay. Okay, thanks.
You need a detailed map?
We biologically traced
Sergeant Laureline to here.
What's she doing out by the Galana Sea?
No idea, sir. She stole a vehicle.
She headed into the Red Zone,
and we lost track of her.
She must have located the Major.
General, there are three civilians here
who claim to have information
that might interest you.
Show them in.
Ah...
It's you three.
- Our humble respects, General.
- May you be healthy...
- And prosperous.
- What do you want?
We have information
of the utmost importance.
- That we're ready to sell.
- 100 baduls.
- Each.
- Shoot.
Valerian!
Move, lizard.
Valerian? Valerian, do you hear me?
Valerian, wake up. Valerian, please.
Stay with me, Valerian. Come on. Come on.
- What are you doing here?
- I came to get you.
You totaled your SkyJet, remember?
Yeah. I lost it in a curve.
You mean you almost died.
You're lucky I found you.
What about the Commander?
Do we know where he is?
There's no sign of him.
Their spaceship went into a Red Zone.
We gotta find him.
- Let's go.
- Wait.
- Is that all?
- What do you mean?
No "Thank you?" No "Well done?"
I would have done the same for you.
- You little prick.
- Whoa! Hey, hey, hey, chill.
I trusted you more than I trusted myself.
- Isn't that what you wanted?
- No.
You are an amazing woman, Laureline.
It's no wonder I wanna marry you.
Why would I wanna marry
an ungrateful, conceited...
Because you can't live without him.
I mean, look, whenever he wanders off,
you go chasing after him.
I was just doing my job, Major.
Now will you please let me
get back to the mission?
Yeah, sure.
Good.
Sergeant.
Captain, what's going on here?
I report directly
to the Commander Arun Filitt.
- I don't have to...
- I am General Okto-Bar!
In the absence of the Commander,
I am in command on Alpha!
Arrest this man!
And release that one.
I apologize for your mistreatment.
We will take you to a jail
but our doctors will take care of you.
Help us.
If you need my help,
you have to tell me everything you know.
But first of all,
why are you attacking us?
Because you have...
what we need.
Didn't you say that the girl in your dream
- had a Converter just like mine?
- That's right.
So if the animals are native
on their planet then,
surely it's understandable that they want
to retrieve the last living specimen.
Yeah, and they probably
kidnapped the Commander
because they thought he was carrying it.
Yeah, once they find out he's not,
then I'll be the top of their list.
Don't worry, I'm not letting
you go anywhere.
No, I'm not letting you go anywhere.
Wow.
Pretty butterfly.
Sure, but whatever you do,
don't touch them.
- Why?
- Because some of them are...
No!
Valerian!
Laureline!
I'm coming! I'm coming. I'm coming.
Let me go, fatty. Come on, put me down.
Sorry, I'm inedible.
Valerian!
Major, I can read your signal now.
Alex, any ideas?
The only way
to get in without creating
a severe diplomatic incident
is to pass for one of them.
I suggest you try to find a glamopod.
Thanks, Alex.
Have you run a DNA search?
Yes, but it didn't match
any of the 800 million species
- we have in that database.
- Well, how's that possible?
Either it belongs to a
completely unknown species...
Or?
Or this species was deliberately deleted
from the database.
General, the Major has resurfaced
at the edge of the Red Zone.
Which district is he in?
Paradise Alley.
Notify all units.
All units.
Search alert. Major Valerian.
Not dangerous. Find and assist.
- Can I help you?
- Sure you can. Move.
Good. Now slide your gun into my holster.
Hold still.
Hi, sugar.
Do you wanna ride?
Hey.
Hey, you wanna fly?
I'm allergic to feathers.
My hero.
You got the wrong guy.
Huh. I...
I don't speak French.
Hello.
Come on, out. Pervert.
Hey, cowboy.
You've come to the right spot.
It's the best damn club
on the whole space station.
- Hey, Jolly.
- I'll be with you in a second.
I'm looking for something special.
Well, of course you are.
Whatever it is you want,
I got it.
- I'm not so sure about...
- Well, I am.
Tell me, what is it you want?
What are you looking for?
- A glamopod.
- You are so lucky.
I got the best one
in the whole universe. Come on!
Jolly.
Come on.
Hey, I work for the government.
If you want to avoid a diplomatic incident
you better let me go right now.
Look, listen. I didn't come
here to get a makeover.
I need to leave. Do you understand?
I can't believe it.
I'm not here to try on a stupid dress!
Call your chief or a translator
so we can at least communicate.
Do you understand what I am saying?
Hmm.
Okay.
This is where you lose
the hardware, soldier boy.
I'd rather hold onto it. I'm on duty.
Yeah, well, unfortunately rules are rules,
and this is a place where
we make love, not war.
Here's your ticket.
Don't lose it.
Can we make a deal?
Let's not talk about business, can we?
Let's talk pleasure.
What kinda music are you into, huh?
You like techno? Macro? Bio? Nano?
- I'm more retro.
- Oh. Me, too.
Oldies are goodies.
Sit down. Relax. And enjoy the show.
Ha!
I don't know how long
I can keep doing this.
So what'll it be, soldier?
Look, that was really cool,
but not exactly what
I'm looking for right now.
Well I have a whole lot more in stock
if you just tell me what you have in mind.
I have a lot in mind.
And no time for this. I'll pass.
Listen, I have a problem
and I really need your help.
You didn't like my performance?
No, no, yeah. I...
- I loved it. Absolutely.
- I started at age four.
Learning my trade in all the top schools.
- I can play anyone or anything.
- I'm sure you can.
I know all of Shakespeare
by heart if you want.
Poetry maybe? You like poetry?
- Sure.
- Rimbaud? Verlaine?
Tough choice.
"I'm afraid of a kiss...
Like the kiss of a bee...
I suffer like this...
And wake endlessly...
I'm afraid of a kiss."
How about I tell you
what I really have in mind?
- No, quit screaming.
- How'd you get a gun?
Hey...
Major Valerian, I advise you
to put that gun down.
- And I advise you to sit down.
- Okay, okay. Okay.
- Please! No! Don't shoot me!
- What the hell is that?
That is you, when you were 10.
You're not going to
shoot yourself, are you?
- Will you go back to normal, please?
- Okay, okay.
No. Not this normal. The other one.
Okay, okay.
Thank you. What's your name?
Whatever you want it to be, sweetie.
I don't have time for your games, sweetie.
Come on, tell me, what's your name?
Bubble.
Look, Bubble, I lost my partner.
If you help me find her,
I'll set you free.
What good is freedom when
you're an illegal immigrant
- far away from home?
- I work for the government.
I'll get you an ID pass. You have my word.
If I leave, Jolly will kill me.
No, Jolly won't kill anybody ever again.
So what do you say, Bubble?
You really liked my performance?
Best I ever saw.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, I'm gonna take 10.
You two keep an eye on old soldier boy.
He seems like a real freak to me.
Okay, Bubble, get off me.
All right, all right,
I'm doing this.
Hey, you good?
Thanks.
- You wanna go in there?
- Yeah, but no foreigners are allowed.
The only way in
is to look like one of them.
Oh, no, no, no! I've never played
a Boulan Bathor before.
What? Are you an artist or not?
Yes, but I need time to get into my role,
and capture my movements and behaviors,
and character's arc.
We do a couple rehearsals,
you give me some notes...
Well, a little improv never hurt anyone.
Let's go.
All right.
Turn around.
Ugh.
This is not right.
I need a manicure.
Don't you think the hat
might be a little bit over the top?
Uh... Uh...
Never mind.
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
what are you doing?
Give me a second
to get the hang of it.
Hurry, people are staring at us.
I told you I needed rehearsals.
This is a heavy role.
Much better.
You're doing good.
General, we've picked up
the Major's trail again.
Finally. Where is he?
In Boulan Bathor territory.
In the...
Nobody gets in there.
And definitely not out of there.
We'll need reinforcements.
Inform the Minister.
Yes, sir.
So how did you come
to lose your partner?
- Because I'm stupid.
- What do you mean?
All I do is flirt and joke.
Oh, trying to be cool
rather than being honest?
Story of my life.
How young were you
when you lost your mom?
Please don't go there right now.
It's okay to be
vulnerable sometimes.
Can we stop this and get back
to the mission, please?
And don't touch anything.
Well, it wouldn't
hurt you to show some weakness.
I'm not good at that.
It will make her feel important.
Yeah, believe me, she's already
the most important thing in my life.
I think he wants us
to join the group.
I'm not sure that's a good idea.
It doesn't look like
he's giving us much choice.
What's going on?
I guess it's lunchtime
for Emperor Boulan Ill.
Bussing tables,
every artist's worst nightmare.
Never mention this to anyone, okay?
Thank your lucky stars
we're not the main course.
Oh...
I'm going to be sick.
There she is.
Wow. You're right, she's a 10.
Hmm?
Hi.
- Something's wrong.
- How about I do a little dance,
- to create a diversion?
- No, thanks.
- You guys are in big trouble!
- I think we should go.
I think you should
let me handle this.
- Valerian!
- I'm in here!
Hey.
You're gonna be a good boy, okay?
Down! Stay!
Laureline, it's me. Valerian.
What?
Oh!
Bubble, get off me.
Yes, you're right, let's go.
Whoo!
Excuse me, Your Highness.
Hey, baby.
I deserved that.
Watch out!
This is a lady. You can't fight her.
Let's talk about this.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
I warned you.
Well, that's what I call a partner.
Whoo-hoo!
Bravo. That was amazing.
I'm very impressed.
Hey.
Trust me on this.
Third Regiment approaching, sir.
- Any news from our agents?
- None.
And the Commander?
Any ransom demands?
Negative. Minister on line.
Okay.
My respects, Minister.
General, you've been
authorized by the council
to assume command of this operation.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you, sir.
But to fulfill my mission, I will need
full access to Commander Filitt's data.
According to regulations, that is
impossible without his explicit agreement.
The Commander may well be dead.
If I am to succeed in my new assignment,
I need to know everything.
- Access granted.
- Thank you, sir.
Declassify.
Request file on the Planet Mül.
Request authorized.
Huh. "The Conflict
with the Southern Territories."
"The war against the Azien Korn
led to the destruction of Planet Mül."
Tell me more about the planet.
"The planet was uninhabited."
Who's in charge of this operation?
This does not smell good.
Told you there was a door.
Someone didn't look over the plans
before they came rushing in. As usual.
What, you'd rather I'd showed up
after the main event?
I'd rather you took me someplace
other than a giant trash can.
Bubble?
Bubble, where are you? Where is she?
She was right behind us.
I'm here.
What's wrong?
I must've been injured during the fight.
Bubble, tell me what to do.
Nothing you can do.
Anyway, where I'm from,
life is more painful than death.
Don't say that.
Unfortunately, it's true.
Life's a drag when you don't have
an identity to call your own.
You do have an identity.
You're the greatest artist I've ever seen.
I thank you.
It was my pleasure performing for you.
I leave you my kingdom.
Take good care of it.
I will.
But most importantly...
Yeah?
Take good care of her.
Love her without measure.
"There's beggary in love
that can be reckoned."
Let's go.
All the battleships have docked, General.
Good. I want Section 1
operative as soon as possible.
What are those K-tron doing there?
The Commander programmed them personally.
- They can't be deactivated.
- Great.
That's all we need.
Do you have any idea where we're going?
Yeah, sure. I mean...
- I guess.
- You're sure or you guess?
Look, I know it sounds strange but it...
The Princess, she's guiding me.
The Princess? She's guiding you?
Yeah. Look, it's hard to explain,
but it's like she's been
with me the whole time.
Wait.
You mean to tell me
that you've had a woman
inside of you since the beginning?
Laureline, can we just keep going, please?
Sure.
- Ladies first.
- Ha! Hilarious.
Go, fill it in! Fill it in!
Over there!
Captain Kris. Section 1 operational.
General?
Proceed. A unit of K-trons will join you.
- That won't be necessary.
- Commander's orders, not mine.
Copy that. Move on!
We've been manipulated from the start.
What do you mean?
We're in the middle of the Dead Zone
and we can breathe properly.
It seems there's no sign of contamination.
The Commander's fully aware of what's
behind this so-called absolute evil.
What?
Pearls.
My name is Tsûuri. I am the Emperor's son.
Great. How about
you introduce us to Daddy?
He is expecting you.
Try to contact the General.
Get everyone down here.
I'll buy us some time.
How about you run for backup for a change?
Unbelievable.
Follow me.
I'd like you to meet
my father, the Emperor.
My name is Haban-Limaï
and this is my wife, Aloi.
We're pleased to welcome you here.
My son sensed the presence of his sister,
Princess Lïhio-Minaa, in you.
It seems she chose you.
What do you mean?
At the moment of passing,
Pearls release all the energy
left in their body
in the form of a wave,
which travels through space and time.
Sometimes it finds a benevolent host.
Lïho-Minaa chose you
to be the guardian of her soul.
Told you.
My daughter.
I'm so happy to see you.
Same here.
I mean, she is, too.
What exactly happened
to you and your people?
Our planet was a true paradise, on which
we lived in harmony with the elements.
Our main activity was fishing for the
pearls who possessed phenomenal energy.
They fertilized our lands,
controlled the winds and tides.
Three times a year we gave to the earth,
what the sea had given us.
We lived like this, in harmony,
for centuries and centuries.
Until the day of the apocalypse.
In the sky over our planet,
other people blindly
fought out a brutal war.
A war between people we didn't even know.
Missiles loaded, sir.
Engage fusio-missiles.
Do you confirm, sir?
Yes, I do.
At your command.
By the grace of God.
Your daughter died during the battle.
Yes, like six million others.
What happened after the explosion?
We drifted in space for many years.
Aboard a vessel we salvaged
from the wreckage,
and that was half-destroyed.
This new environment was
quite different from ours.
And at first, we needed time
to understand it,
absorbing the vast knowledge
stored in its database.
We learned languages and mathematics,
physics, chemistry,
and philosophy.
We learned about the millions of planets
and stars and moons
in a universe we never knew existed.
And we learned of the countless species
who inhabit this universe.
Including humans, the ones
who destroyed our planet.
Time has not dimmed
the memories of our loss,
but it has allowed us to let go
of our anger toward those responsible.
Then, one day, we were picked up
by scrap dealers traveling the galaxy.
After a few years, their hold was full.
And they went off to sell their cargo
on a huge construction site.
- Alpha.
- Yes.
The City of a Thousand Planets,
where for hundreds of years,
so many species
have shared their knowledge
and intelligence with each other.
In the shadows of Alpha,
we lived undetected,
all the while watching and learning
from each of them.
Until we acquired both the knowledge,
and the materials
to build a vessel of our own.
Our planet is gone forever,
but with what we have learned,
we are now able to replicate
and restore our lost world.
Amazing.
There are only two things that we lack.
A Mül Converter.
And a pearl.
The only one Tsûuri managed to salvage.
We are survivors,
but that makes us witnesses.
Witnesses of a past that humans want to
erase and forget forever.
We can forgive, but how can we forget?
So we left you no choice
but to steal the Converter,
and Tsûuri hired a professional.
Igon Siruss.
But Major Valerian intervenes
and retrieves the Converter.
Which left you with only one choice.
Kidnap the Commander
and force him to tell you the truth.
You know our story now.
Our destiny is in your hands.
Major, arrest these creatures immediately.
They kidnapped me.
They're extremely dangerous.
They're Pearls from the Planet Mül.
I heard their ridiculous story.
That's impossible.
Mül was uninhabited.
Their existence proves
the contrary, doesn't it?
I am telling you
there was no life on the planet.
The detectors were categorical.
Arrest them.
How can you be so sure?
Because I read the reports and...
And you were on board.
Yes. Yes, I was on board.
And we had much more
serious things to worry about.
Our cruisers were being decimated.
We lost 500,000 soldiers in a day.
It was complete carnage!
You were so preoccupied you didn't see
the detectors indicating
signs of life on the planet.
Or even worse. Perhaps you knew the planet
was inhabited and you sacrificed it.
Commander, the planet is inhabited.
- By primitive life forms.
- No, Commander.
I have detected a complex language
and huge cerebral energy.
Major.
History is on the march and neither you
nor a bunch of savages
are gonna stand in its way.
So when you realized survivors from Planet
Mül were living in the heart of Alpha,
you decided to erase
any trace of your mistake,
rather than accept the consequences.
I want no survivors.
And you destroyed all the evidence
that Major Samk had against you.
What did you expect me to do?
It was the only way!
Admitting to an error on this scale
would have exposed our
government to colossal damages
and compensation claims.
Our economy would never recover.
In one instance, we would have lost
our supremacy and our leadership.
There would have been immediate sanctions,
and it's a pretty good bet that
we would have been banished from Alpha
and denied access to the greatest
market of knowledge and intelligence.
Is that what you would have wanted
for your fellow citizens?
Leading them into ruin and degradation?
Forcing them to go backwards 1,000 years?
Our Council saw fit to protect
our citizens first and foremost.
Is that not its duty? And mine?
And yours?
Or would you rather risk wrecking
our economy for the sake of a bunch of...
Savages?
You are totally under the
influence of these creatures.
Do not confuse the issue.
He's the threat!
He's the enemy!
You are your own worst enemy, Commander.
Unless you make peace with your past,
you won't have a future.
Major, I order you to arrest this man.
Can we talk man-to-man for a second?
Major, what are you doing?
I taught him how to do that.
Whew!
Nice talk.
Move on, move on, move on!
Section 1 is entering the Red Zone.
Prepare Section 2 for an advance also.
Look, this was a lot of fun,
but we gotta report back to our people.
Here. That's yours.
We'll make this right, I promise.
Let's get this guy out.
Whoa, what are you doing?
I'm giving them back the Converter.
No.
The pearl is useless without this.
Yeah, but...
Will you give us a second, please?
What?
That Converter is government property.
Most likely, the last one
in the whole universe.
Oh. So you buy into the Commander's
"What's mine is mine
and what's yours is mine" philosophy?
No, I buy into my oath of allegiance.
We have no authority to hand it over.
The Federation messed up
and must make amends.
Yeah, I agree, but that's not
for us to decide.
- Leave it to the courts.
- They're 18 light years away, Valerian.
Only we can make this right.
Laureline, I'm a soldier.
I play by the rules.
It's what makes me who I am.
You see?
That's why I don't want to marry you,
because you really don't know
what love is.
Come on, this has nothing to do with love.
That's where you're wrong.
Love is more powerful
than anything else, Valerian.
It breaks all rules and laws,
and overpowers any army or government.
Just look at her.
For one second,
put yourself in her position.
She lost all of her people and her child,
and she's willing to forgive.
That's real love.
It's the trust you place in someone else,
and I thought I could be
that someone else for you.
- But clearly...
- You can.
You are.
I'd die for you.
I'm not asking you to die for me.
I'm asking you to trust me.
All right, give it to 'em.
Thank you.
We are to blame
for the loss of your planet,
and we'd be honored
to help you get it back.
Here.
It means, "Thank you."
Spread out. Spread out.
Captain, we're locked on to you.
Any sign of contamination or radiation?
Zero trace of either.
It doesn't make any sense.
Didn't you say
you wanted to go to the beach?
Our daughter made a good choice.
She can rest in peace now.
We must leave now.
May you and your people live in peace
wherever you may venture
in space and time.
Explosives in place, General.
We are operational.
Received. Evacuate the zone.
You have four minutes.
Copy that.
Father, there are hundreds of soldiers
- all around the spaceship.
- We will be gone in a minute.
The troops are in position,
you don't have a minute.
You have no means of communication
with the outside world?
If we stop jamming signals,
we are defenseless.
If you don't allow me to communicate
with them you'll be defenseless forever.
Just one call.
- Disarm the signal.
- Thank you!
The wall stopped moving.
Something's going on.
Maintain your position.
We're analyzing the data.
I can't believe they'd do that.
The General followed procedure.
Yeah, I hate procedure.
Captain, the data shows
that they have built some kind of vessel
beyond the wall.
Contact with the enemy.
Give me a physical description.
Same creatures
who kidnapped the Commander.
They showing any signs of hostility?
Not really.
- Are they armed?
- No.
General, we're picking up a signal
from the 2005 Destiny module.
- What?
- Sounds like Major Valerian.
- Patch him through.
- Major, you're on line with the General.
- Major?
- Yeah.
Major Valerian and Sergeant Laureline.
We're alive and on the inside of the wall.
Call off the assault immediately.
Major, I can't read your DNA codes.
You know the procedure.
I have to be certain it's you.
There is no time for dumbass procedures!
We are here with a whole species of people
you've already wiped out once!
The Pearls of Planet Mül!
So tell your men to back off
before you commit a second genocide!
- That's definitely her temper.
- Planet Mül was uninhabited.
Come on. You know that's not true.
The Commander was there.
He gave the orders.
And then he organized this whole procedure
to eliminate any survivors,
the living proof of his mistake.
- Stop the procedure.
- Maybe that would explain
why the Commander was
interrogating that creature.
Is the Commander with you?
Come on! Wakey, wakey.
- You've got a call.
- What?
Let's go, my friend. Time to confess.
Hello?
No DNA code, but voice waves match.
This is General Okto-Bar.
Do you read me, Commander?
What's going on?
We are ready to activate
the explosive device
in accordance with the orders you gave.
Do you confirm those orders,
or do you have anything to tell me,
that would enable me
to suspend the assault?
I am a soldier.
A soldier will always choose
death over humiliation.
Annihilate them all.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I didn't give the orders!
Captain, cease fire immediately!
It's not us, it's the K-trons.
They're shooting at us!
Come on, you...
I'm gonna go give Tsûuri some backup.
Keep an eye on him.
Oh, he's not going anywhere.
Get down! Take cover!
Alex, load me up with all you've got!
- Copy that.
- Thanks.
- Neza, stop this countdown now!
- Yes, sir!
Hurry, Neza!
- How much time left?
- Ten seconds!
Hurry!
Neza.
Check for survivors.
Captain, status report?
Nothing's left. Just a gaping hole.
They left with their spaceship.
Everything's vanished.
And our agents? Valerian and Laureline?
- No, nothing.
- And the Commander?
Is anyone there?
Wait, I hear something.
There's a body!
Get me down from here, you children!
It's the Commander.
Is he alive?
Affirmative. Alive and kicking!
Good.
Arrest him.
Help!
Do you have
any idea where they left us?
We're two hours away
from vacation.
I fired the distress beacons.
- Two hours?
- Yeah, I know.
- Two hours alone with me, what a drag.
- Hmm.
No kidding. It's basically an eternity.
Hey.
Now that our mission's over
maybe we can finish our conversation.
What conversation?
We were talking about the future.
Really? And what does the future hold?
You.
Me.
Us.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Valerian.
That is so romantic.
Did you really think of this yourself?
Yeah. You mean so much to me, you know?
Laureline...
will you do me the honor
of becoming my wife?
For better or worse?
Uh, worse? Is that negotiable?
No.
All right, then.
Is that a yes?
It's a maybe.
I'm confused. Is this how love works?
No, this is how I work.
You spent a day in a woman's body,
did you not learn anything?
Yeah.
I did learn something.
What?
I want only your name on my playlist.
♪ I gotta find myself gonna find it now
I gotta be a man I gotta find him now ♪
♪ I gotta be a man, I gotta be the man ♪
♪ They wanna take me down
Wanna see me crawl ♪
♪ I gotta be a man I gotta find him now
I gotta be a man I gotta be the man ♪
♪ I gotta find myself gonna find it now ♪
♪ I gotta be a man I gotta find him now
I gotta be a man I gotta be the man ♪
♪ When I come to town for the last time
Pull up in a fast car for the first time ♪
♪ I'm gonna say goodbye
You didn't see me cry ♪
♪ I got a million on my soul
I go build an army on my own ♪
♪ They put a bounty on my soul ♪
♪ Won't you leave me alone more
Oh leave me alone more ♪
♪ I gotta be a man I gotta be a man ♪
♪ Won't you leave me alone more
Oh leave me alone more ♪
♪ I gotta be a man I gotta be a man ♪
♪ I gotta find myself gonna find it now
I gotta be a man I gotta find him now ♪
♪ I gotta be the man ♪
♪ Your stare makes me freeze
But I can't stay still ♪
♪ Those eyes keep me up longer
Than any other pill ♪
♪ And I know being together
We feel like forever ♪
♪ But now more than ever
I feel everything Feeling everything ♪
♪ You make me feel so crazy
I've never felt so sane ♪
♪ Beaten up by love
But the feelings still remain ♪
♪ You should know
If you want it it's yours
♪ So come and get it right now ♪
♪ More than ever I feel everything
Feeling everything ♪
♪All I got I'm yours
I'll give it to you be mine ♪
♪ You're in my brain I'm yours
And in my heart too be mine ♪
♪ Because I am yours I want you
If you want me too I want you ♪
♪ Tell me you want me too
'Cause I'll give it all to you ♪
♪ I'm scared that I'm falling
Come catch me I'm falling ♪
♪ My heart is calling you can't stop me
roaring I'm soaring I'm sky high ♪
♪ I'm scared that I'm falling
I'm blind and I'm falling ♪
♪ My love is calling
You can't stop me roaring I'm soaring ♪
♪ Come jump with me and fly ♪
♪ Never thought I'd fall like this ♪
♪ I've tripped right into
This eternal bliss ♪
♪ And I know being together
We feel like forever ♪
♪ But now more than ever I feel everything
Feeling everything ♪
♪ All I got I'm yours
I'll give it to you be mine ♪
♪ You're in my brain I'm yours
And my heart too be mine ♪
♪ Because I'm yours
If you want me too ♪
♪ Tell me you want me too
'Cause I'll give it all to you ♪
♪ I'm scared that I'm falling
Feeling everything ♪
♪ Feeling everything ♪